You
I've been thinking we have a lot of only children in our group, huh?
Nobody else has a little brother, but me. I have my big sister Miki. I
Guess that's pretty much it
Yeah, but what's most shocking about our posse is that she was also an older sibling
What did none of you know
It's not that many so calm down a few days ago. He invited me over to hang and incidentally I found out
back
Appreciate you having me
It's fine just try to keep quiet roger that and don't touch me
Oh
Maybe sis yep three years younger I thought a blood relative might be different
Go away! Welcome home, Miss Buffa!
They look alike, but she treated him kind of cold
Get out
Iorta being a big brother is nuts
You learn something new every day
He's fairly chill when he's not at school weird, right?
Well, that's hard to picture
Sub nerds! Let's go eat our weight in burgers after class, okay?
Uh
You need to start acting more responsibly, sheesh!
Sheesh!
Uh
Oh
Then
ya
G
もうできないあの頃に君を残したまま
記憶の中では晴れ者の部屋
惹かれ合えばさらば知りたくない
思い出せば今もふわっと香る
君と僕は同じ色香水
ほんの少し背伸びをして歩いた道
ビリドロの靴 移り変わる季節模様
きっと消えない今日は言えない
元通りにはもうできない
あの頃に隠した本物はどこ
怒ってくれない分かってくれない
思ってもただ募ってしまうだけ
懐かしい匂いとこの歌が残る
バイパー
I heard you loosened it up with Yuki, though.
What? Really?
Yeah. For example...
Bye-bye!
Oh, yes. Bye.
Yanagin, say bye-bye!
Right.
Yanagin, bye-bye!
Okay. Bye-bye.
Benny, can't believe you said it! You are so cute!
That girl is a force to be reckoned with. No doubt about it.
Thanks for waiting. What's going on?
Just entertaining myself watching Ayasaki mess with Yanagin.
Huh. Oh, so are you girls heading home, too? Bye-bye!
Bye. See you guys around.
Of course.
Ciao.
Catch you later.
See?
Huh. Wonder why.
It's not exactly rocket science.
Hey, here's an idea.
You could always call everyone by their first name.
Now start using your first name, too.
It's times like these I really envy Yorta's peppy personality.
Hey, Akane.
Now you go.
I'm really not sure.
I've never once used a friend's first name before.
Sorry, but this might be hard for me.
Come on, man. At least throw in a dude.
No more politeness, starting now.
What?
Knock it off. You're obviously bothering him.
Oh, no. He's certainly not. I assure you.
Because, well, I too recognize the fact that I'm not close with anybody.
That I use my words to keep others at a distance.
But that's not to say I wouldn't like to become better friends with you all.
On the contrary, I'd like that very much.
Hmm?
Was there a meeting I didn't get a memo for or something?
He's also a new addition to the friend group, and he started things off way worse than you.
I hated his guts. Now look how close we are.
Huh?
You couldn't pay me to snuggle up with the prez like that not in a million years.
Those two are amazing.
They sapped Yorta's energy in one fell swoop.
Go on and explain to Yanagi what good buddies we are.
All it took was a little AC and ice cream.
What the heck are you talking about?
We are really brothers from another mother.
Yorta key's in that brotherhood too.
That's why I voted for ya.
Boys are weird.
And that's my cue to go find Yuki.
I've never felt closer to you, friends.
Brotherhood.
Rock, paper, scissors settles any argument with your brush.
That doesn't always work and you know it.
Don't listen to him. His skills at that game are trash.
You lose ten times more than I do.
Guess I'll have to try.
Um...
Well, I thought I was pretty good at rock, paper, scissors.
You're there every time you lose.
Count the number of trips that you've taken to the vending machine.
Then I'll make it a point to win.
Um, Ishikawa.
If it's alright with you, I'd like to try calling you Toru.
Sure.
Akane?
What about me, bro?
One at a time. Best to take things like this slow.
Okay.
But I want to be next!
Does it go both ways?
Hmm?
Are you going to start calling him by his first name too?
Be kind of lame if I didn't.
Don't want him being the only one, right?
Wasn't that what started this conversation?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
I have a personal blacklist, you know.
And Yonaki's on it.
For now.
Why? What did pure soul like him ever do to you?
Just a joke.
What?
Forget I said it.
You really need to work on your sense of humor.
Miyamura?
Hmm?
I won't take them away.
And what exactly are these things that you won't be taking from me?
Has he mugged you before?
Is that the reason he's on your blacklist?
Leave me alone!
Come on, out with it!
Hmm?
You dummy!
You're king, dummy, Akane!
And there he goes.
That strange, beautiful boy.
Yeah, because he used your first name?
Just accept that you're wrong already.
I'm not.
Look.
How about a third opinion?
Well, it couldn't hurt.
I know the answer is me, so tell him that I'm taller.
No, we're clearly the same height.
Is this stemming from some kind of fight?
It's stemming from Akane approaching me and declaring that he had a random growth spurt.
He doesn't believe it, even though the proof's right in front of him.
So you are fighting.
There's nothing to fight about!
You can't debate something that's fact!
Neither one of us reached 170, but when I said that, he got mad at me!
It's such a petty thing to get upset over Miyamoto.
Though Yanagi getting defensive was juvenile, too.
I apologize.
Hey!
I screwed up first!
I'm way more apologetic!
Did I speak out of turn?
I'm sorry.
You did it again!
I'll reflect on my wrong feelings.
I'm not sure how it happened, but I'm glad these two are such close friends.
I'm sorry.
Dammit, Akane!
Yes?
How do you feel about this one?
Normal.
And this one?
Uh, normal.
Wow.
That's some massive improvement there.
Yo, we're human beings, not inanimate objects.
Get it straight?
Yes, please do.
I'm sorry.
I was just testing Suwata's comfort level when she's around guys.
Ah.
Now I can push my limit to Sengoku.
Wait, so where do I rank on this little chart?
Ha!
Sweet!
Hey, you want some snacks?
So, you're a chocolate lover?
Then get a load of this.
You can have as many as you want.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Literally eating out of the palm of my hand.
It's not a contest.
Just you wait!
Whatever you do, don't open your mouth.
It's all that I ask.
What?
Speak up!
This ain't a library, it's a hallway!
Salutations, Suwata!
What are you hiding for?
You know who I am.
No!
It's called tact.
Please try and learn it.
Wait, what?
Suwata, Yuta's actually a nice guy.
You can trust him.
Miyamura!
So what?
Whether he identifies as a good guy or a bad guy was never the issue at hand.
I gave it my best shot, but I guess it's no dice.
Annoying loudmouths are the absolute worst!
Ugh!
Feels like I swallowed sandpaper.
What?
You coming down with a cold?
You do keep coughing.
Hmm, nah.
I'm pretty sure I'm just losing my voice.
Long as you're not fatigued, you should be okay.
Actually, I am kind of fatigued.
Why are you here if you're sick?
Yeah, you definitely have a fever.
Why are you manhandling me?
I'm a fragile enough flower as it is, even when I'm not under the weather!
And rip my throat.
Go home and rest up if it hurts that bad.
You might be contagious, you big dummy.
Hmm.
So heavy.
Wait.
Excuse me.
So, uh...
Thank you.
You might be contagious, you big dummy.
Hey, you...
Wait.
What?
Man!
A little bit of mouthwash and a good night's rest got me feeling better than ever!
Congrats, dude!
Yeah, hooray!
Don't act so excited.
And why congratulate me?
It isn't like that cold was a big test.
Speaking of, your sister's studying for entrance exams, so I hope you didn't get her sick.
Huh.
Hmm.
Hey, Sawada!
Ah!
Um, hey.
Did you need Yura?
Mm-hmm.
Do you think he's angry with you or something?
Kinda.
Does Yura...
even get angry?
Huh?
He's one of the most laid-back guys I've ever met.
Fuck it!
Wait, are you positive he's upset with you?
Well, laughter is typically a good sign, so I believe you're in the clear.
Uh...
Do you want him to like you?
Huh?
Whoa!
What are you ladies doing out here by your lonesomes?
Huh?
If you're looking for Miyamura, he hasn't made it in yet.
Oh, he has, though!
Oh, were you talking about something?
Huh?
Was it private?
You know what?
Don't answer that.
But I am curious if you had to carry anything else.
The science room is practically on the other side of campus from the second-year classrooms,
so I was worried you'd wind up being tardy.
Were you?
You're so stinking annoying!
Ah!
Ah, she totally hates me.
Yura?
You should work on your timing.
What?
What does that mean?
Hmm.
Okay.
So you're setting your sights on East High, are you?
Yes, sir.
That's quite a lofty goal.
You've put all your eggs in this one basket?
Huh?
You should probably be a little more realistic and aim a rank lower.
I mean, your grades are pretty average.
You're not making marks in a single subject that would be, uh...
Oh, but that's not to say you're completely without options here.
Big dreams are nice, but attainable ones are better, so give it some thought and come back to me.
East High isn't the end-all be-all.
dinner and this guy laughing at you well you're still going to eat starving won't solve anything
fine I'll force it down okay where do you want to go to high school you're gonna laugh too did
I ask you to tell me a joke no I asked about your future East High that's not funny East High is the
most basic name for a school I've ever heard my teacher didn't laugh at the name idiot he laughed
because my grades aren't good enough he did do your grades really suck that much you know sis
you've hurled enough textbooks and notes in my face for me to have a good idea of how you study
let me tell you the pages are barely hanging on to their binding because of the countless times
they've been turned and there are so many highlights you could put the nightly news to shame I see how
hard you work please tell me which teacher had the nerve to laugh at all that effort I would love to
be introduced so I can punch his lights out you're too smart to resort to that so I'll do it for you
why
I don't get it I really don't I try but my grades keep slipping even my teacher thinks I'm a lost cause
except their dreams are nice but attainable ones are better and all my friends have good enough grades
I know they'll get it then there's me
stupid me
I'm stuck what should I do I feel so lost
no matter how much I try and try and try and try something in my brain just doesn't click
the East High uniforms are super ugly anyway if you end up having to try for a lower ranked school
katagiri should be at the top of your list
our uniforms look awesome on everyone I know you'd rock one
the only thing you can do now is your best
but you'll need brain food so make sure you eat
I'm glad I caught you I have a little favor to ask if you're free
hey you ready to study your uh your brother already filled me in
yeah come on in Motoko
um thanks for having me
you can head upstairs and set your stuff down in my room if you want to
it's the first door you see meet you there once I get us drinks
sure sounds good
hello there
hi how are you doing
hello goodbye
okay
those two are probably her brothers
you want me to tutor your sister really I'm honored I was your first pick
it doesn't even have to last more than one session just until you can tell if
she'd be able to test into east high
that sounds fairly doable so sure
and one last thing if it's completely hopeless tell her
seriously
nah I was just goofing
but if you could help prepare her for the next test even a little bit that'd be great
not a problem
that's the face of a big brother
sorry for the wait
hope you like hot chocolate
uh I do
the resemblance between you and your brother's uncanny
do you get that a lot
yeah
I can't really blame people for saying that since my brother and I are both the brooding silent type
wow the silent type
uh I brought textbooks for each class
I take a whole bunch of notes
would you like to go over them
oh we'll get to that later
I know focusing can be kind of tough when you're studying in a place that's new to you
uh
so let's have some girl talk
just put the books down for a second
but but that's not why I'm here
once you've relaxed a little and made yourself more at home we can get to studying
doesn't necessarily have to be girl talk
I have some resident boys on call that can come join us if you'd like
so hey
who was that girl in the hallway
she's the younger sister of our mutual friend
the hoodie's helping her study
if you're ready for cupcakes let me hear you say yeah
yeah
let's give some to Motoko to show our support
okay
you're kidding me
so it's the social norm for middle schoolers to have cell phones now
yeah everybody in my grade has one
dang
oh but I don't have many of my classmates contact info
so I guess it's more like a paperweight
I basically only text my brother
oh so you're close
we couldn't be further apart if we tried
our typical conversation consists of him scolding me through a text message when I come home late
he could be in the next room but he'll use his phone instead of his mouth
sounds close to me
even after what I just told you
you don't think he hates me
you look like you're making a life or death decision
which one is guaranteed to make people pass exams
stop being lame and just pick a stupid charm
I guess I'll go with the biggest one
I'm sorry
all our charms are the same size sir
and then which one's the most expensive
is that for your sister?
she actually wants it sure
why wouldn't she want a gift from her brother?
especially one so thoughtful
hey look it started snowing
sometimes
it's hard
I know I mess up
but even so
I hope she doesn't hate me
it's just gonna be
I Yasuo
It's been a long time since I've seen my dreams
The night is a beautiful night
I'll see you again next time
Long袖のシャツに見覚えある道
少し寂しそうに見えた
胸が苦しくなるけど暖かい
気付いた冬の朝だ
約束するよ
近くにいるから見えないものほど
大事にするよ
言葉にできないんだけどね
お姿をご覧ください
!
You